# Reymart Vega

Caloocan City, Manila, Philippines +63 939 837 9218 reymartvega@gmail.com

Github Linkedin Portfolio

#### Skills:

- Proficient in languages such as JavaScript, HTML, and CSS
- Familiarity with front-end framework such as React.js
- Understanding of back-end frameworks such as Node.js and Express.js
- Knowledge of database technologies such as MySQL and MongoDB,
- Experience with version control systems such as Git
- Experience with MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js) stack
- Proficient in Bootstrap and Material UI frameworks for front-end development
- Familiarity with Figma for UI/UX design

## **Projects:**

Admin Dashboard: A client-side Admin dashboard that shows the process of fetching data from the API, Technologies used on front-end are React.js, MaterialUI, Redux for state management, Material DataGrid for Tables and Nivo for the charts. The technologies used on back-end are Node.js Express.js, MongoDB, and Redux Toolkit Query for API calls.

<u>ShutInPH</u>: The aim of this project is to create a simple service website that provides clients with information about the services offered. The technologies used on front-end are React.js and Bootstrap and the technologies used in backend are Node.js Express.js, and MongoDB.

<u>Portfolio</u>: The portfolio website is designed to impress potential clients or collaborators by showcasing my skills, experience, and accomplishments in a visually appealing and professional manner. The technologies used are React.js and Bootstrap.

## Work Experience:

## SAN MIGUEL CORPORATION, REEFERVAN MERCHANDISER, NOVEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

- Ensured that the retail stores are stocked with products.
- Tracked inventory levels and report any issues or shortages to the management.

#### JANICX DISKLESS SOLUTIONS, COMPUTER TECHNICIAN, AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2019

- Maintained computer systems in some Internet Cafes in Manila Area.
- Created Diskless servers and workstations for an Architecture firm.

## DNA ENGINEERING AND CONSTRUCTION, ELECTRICIAN, FEBRUARY 2017 - JUNE 2017

Installed and repaired electrical wiring, systems and fixtures in the building.

## **Certifications:**

UI/UX DESIGN USING FIGMA, MSTCONNECT, 2023

CCBOOT AND PFSENSE FIREWALL INSTALLATION, NEXUS EDUCATION, 2017

#### **Education:**

Zuitt Web Developer Program (MERN Stack) January 9 - Feb 23, 2023

Main Course Package [Completer / Attended]

ACCESS COMPUTER AND TECHNICAL COLLEGES INC June 2018 - March 2020

Computer Science (Undergraduate)

CSHCI June 2016 - September 2016

Electrical Installation and Management NCII

## References:

Available upon request.